Oh, fuck, yeah.
Look at me. Right there.
Oh, that's so fucking sexy.
Such a nasty little girl.
Oh, yeah. On your knees.
Right there.
That's where I want you.
Oh, fuck, that ass is so good.
Get the fuck up.
Right there.
- Fuck me.
- Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah!
Next?
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Please place four fingers on the scanner.
Thank you. Now your thumb.
Thank you.
May I see your passport, please?
Yes.
- Any other nationalities besides Swedish?
- No.
You here for business or pleasure?
Pleasure.
Can you hold up your ID, please?
Okay. Can you hold up the paper
to show today's date?
Okay. And...what is your date of birth?
Uh, 27th of April, 1999.
Do you know what you're here for?
Yes.
Do you know how much you're getting paid?
- Yes.
- How much are you getting paid?
$900.
Are you under the influence
of drugs or alcohol?
- No.
- You know you can stop this shoot
- any time you deem fit?
- Yes.
Okay, are you prepared to show your test
and see the talent's test?
Yes.
You have any no's, do's or don'ts?
- Okay.
We need for you to start
filling out this paperwork, please.
This is your 2257,
your consent for a sexually explicit act.
Okay.
Don't give me that shit.
Hey!
You look like the innocent girl next door.
Do me a favour, grab a seat.
- Bear, we're all good to go?
- Uh, almost.
All right, so, Brian over here,
this creepy semi-middle aged man
- is gonna be fucking your sweet, uh...
- Semi?
I'm being nice here.
Your sweet, 18-year-old, brand-new vagina.
So, as a first-timer,
you're gonna gradually...
We wanna see you maybe looking like
his dick's a little too big,
a little too painful at the beginning,
but still enjoyable,
you don't need to look like it's hurting
like crazy, but just act like it's, "Oh!"
And gradually go to just straight...
insanity.
In fact, why don't you start
getting ready, uh, Brian,
if you need a minute.
Actually, I'm almost there.
If you're ready,
if everybody's ready to go...
I'm ready.
This motherfucker
looks like he's ready.
Bear, do me a favour,
let's get her the girlie stuff.
All right, here we go.
Got you a little set box,
all the goodies that you need here. Um...
We have lube, if you want,
silicone or water-based -
your choice, whichever you prefer.
And, um, have this for you.
We have hand sanitizer for you,
we have tissue, paper towel,
we have wipes.
What is it?
It's a douche.
Yeah, it's to clean your, um...
to clean your pussy out.
So, you're nice and fresh for me.
You don't wash pussy in Sweden?
Sorry.
Okay.
Hey, are you ready?
Right, but if you feel uncomfortable
and, like, you don't want to shoot,
nobody's forcing you to shoot.
We can always, obviously,
have another girl sent here.
That's not the issue.
Making sure you're comfortable
is the priority.
I feel so stupid.
So, you know, what we call this
in the business is simply stage fright.
I mean, some of the biggest girls,
biggest names in the business
were exactly where you are today.
In fact, it feels like déjà vu.
Just a normal part of being amateur
or doing something for the first time
is it comes with a
little bit of nervousness.
But... I feel like
that's all part of stage fright
so you just have to
overcome it and push past it.
But no pressure.
So, I kind of need you to be a little shy,
know what I mean?
If you just came in like,
"Gimme the dick!" And, "Where's this?"
It would be a little bit weird.
It wouldn't match the scene we need.
We need that innocence,
that shyness, that nervousness.
The innocence.
All right, everybody ready to go?
Tweak this light over just a little bit.
Have it hit her face a little bit more.
And watch out for that stand.
Okay. My bad.
All right, Bella,
remember what we spoke about?
I'm gonna ask you
some questions about yourself.
I want you to be sexy
for the viewer at home.
Uh, the guys at home
want to get to know you.
I want you to look at the camera always.
Don't look at me, look at the camera,
'cause you're looking
at the guy at home. Okay?
About ten seconds,
we're gonna start rolling, so...
- Picture's up. You ready?
- Yup.
Action.
- Hi, there.
- Hi.
So what's your name?
Bella Cherry.
- Oh, that's a cute name.
- Thank you.
And a pretty face.
- So, what are you gonna do today?
- I'm gonna do my first porn.
- Your first one, huh?
- Mm-hm.
- How old are you, Bella Cherry?
- I'm 19.
19.
Cool, let's see the rest of you.
Oh, yeah, nice.
Those are cute little titties.
Now spread your pussy for me.
Yeah, does that feel good? It looks good.
Why don't you come down here
and show me how well you can suck dick.
Look up at me. Like that.
- Actually, let's do it again.
- Cut, guys.
One more time. And pull
his pants all the way down.
Yeah,
pull the pants all the way down
and tell me how big the dick is.
Okay.
Gimme big eyes
when you look at the camera.
- Big eyes like you're surprised.
- Okay.
All right, action. Whenever you're ready.
There we go.
Oh, wow, it's so big.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, look at me like that.
Yeah, suck that dick.
All the way down. That's it. Good girl.
Get your legs like this...
- All right, lean back.
- Okay.
There you go.
Fuck, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, baby.
- You're so deep.
Yeah, yeah, look at the dick
going in and out of your pussy.
- A little forward. Right there. Ready?
- Bring this leg back.
Bring your left leg back.
More, more, right there.
A little this way.
You're having another orgasm.
So, build it up for me. Thirty seconds.
Fuck, yeah.
Pound that little pussy.
- Such a nasty little girl.
- Ready?
Say "bye."
Bye.
- Good job!
- Clean up!
- Clean up on aisle two.
- Pretty good for your first time.
- Thank you!
- You're a natural.
I'll high five after you clean up.
- Can I have my phone?
- You want your phone?
- Give the lady her phone.
- Okay.
Just don't touch her hands until she...
Oh, no!
- This is it, right?
- I licked them off.
- That was disgusting.
- Fuck you.
She put his cum on my shirt.
This girl's trying to be pro.
Let's wrap this up
and get everything for the next scene.
I'm gonna go ahead and get
this downloaded and get it started.
Give her a towel and everything,
get her going to the shower
so we can get her paid
and get her out of here.
When the camera came on and you were like,
"I'm here, I'm ready to do this,"
and you just morphed
into this dick-taking actress.
But, like, what do I need to know
to be the next big porn star?
Next big porn star, I mean...
Shit.
Well, I mean, personally,
I think the most important thing is
you need to actually enjoy your
line of work, enjoy what you do.
You know, a lot of people in the business,
you can obviously tell
right away on camera,
they don't look like they're
enjoying themselves.
It also aggravates the crew and
usually you don't get hired again.
No, you did really good there.
Very, very special quality...
going on about you.
- So, are you staying in a model house?
- Yes. For now, at least.
- Oh. Where?
- Um, here.
- Like which model house?
- Models Direct.
- Whoa.
- Huh.
- Mike.
- Yeah.
- Mike's place.
- All right.
- Oh, man. I mean...
- How's that?
How's that going so far?
I mean, I'm not really used to,
um, hanging out with girls.
You gotta stay away from
them girls. They're like...
I know what you mean. It's all drama
and talking shit behind your back.
It's just not really my thing.
They'll steal from you, they'll lie,
they'll be like, "Oh, yeah,
we both like lattes, we're best friends!”
A week later she's trying
to steal your next gig
'cause she's not getting work.
You look very smart
and intelligent.
I mean, I don't think you're looking for
money to take care of a habit
of any sort of kind
other than taking care of yourself, so...
Okay, so...
like, what really drew you out here?
This is a long way from home.
- Like, seriously?
- Yeah.
My dad raped me when I was young.
- So I feel like I... I can't...
- That's not funny.
You're a... Ooh.
Everyone thinks everyone
has a daddy issue like that
but that's just not true, so... okay.
I'm just out here because I want to fuck.
Okay. I mean...
And, like, no, I'm out here
because, like, Swedes,
they just suck.
They're boring.
Like, they enjoy
feeling sorry for themselves.
Okay. Kind of like, uh...
you did today at your scene.
Oh, I cannot believe
I almost chickened out.
I was this close to not doing it.
You were fine, man.
Everybody gets that
little bit of nervousness.
I remember the first time I performed.
I literally thought my dick
was gonna fall off.
Wait, what? You're a porn star?
Uh, no. I wouldn't say "star."
I'm more of a...fetish. Uh, I'm a type.
What do you mean, type?
You know that list you were filling out
at the beginning of the day?
Yeah.
At the very bottom, there was something.
You remember what it was?
Interracial.
Interracial!
The most extreme act you can do
in porn. The most extreme.
I mean, this is even beyond double-anal,
triple-anal, DP,
it's interracial.
That sounds a bit racist.
It sounds racist because...
.it is racist.
Ashley!
Fucking disgusting.
Come on!
Stupid Muppet.
There's boobs in this episode, I think.
Pizza delivery!
Do you want to come
over and eat pizza with us?
I'm making an omelette.
Come on, you have to come over.
We're gonna watch Game of Thrones.
- I'm good.
- Fuck your omelette!
Yeah, pizza makes your butt big,
come watch Game of Thrones with us.
Ew.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ouch, damn it!
Are you taking a shit?
No.
Hey, princess,
open the fucking door.
There you go.
Go for Mike.
Uh, we got about four models
available for Wednesday.
What do you need?
I can give you Jasmine,
boy-girl shoot, for 1,000.
Is she doing her own hair and make-up
or you doing wardrobe?
So, Bella Cherry here is actually
brand-new, fresh from Sweden.
Oh, a Swedish virgin.
Yes.
And Joy here is from Florida,
been in the business two months,
but her first time in LA.
Oh, a southern slut. We like them here.
I do everything. Anal, DPs,
gang bangs, blow bangs.
- Okay.
- I'm a whore.
Everything. Gang bang,
cream pie, blow bang, anal.
- Everything.
- Under the sun.
- Absolutely.
Okay.
I want to start off
with the regular stuff.
So, like, solo, boy-girl, girl-girl.
- What about anal?
- Uh, not yet.
Never tried it?
I have. I just want to keep
some cards up my sleeve for later.
- You know?
- Okay, clever girl.
I need to take some pictures of you girls,
so please take your clothes off.
Oh, the Florida girl is fast, huh?
She's done that before.
I know how to get clothes off in a rush.
Okay, and let's see here.
As you can see, no tattoos on her.
And Bella has a couple tattoos.
How many tattoos do you have?
- Uh, about 25.
- 25...
Yeah, look happy. Okay, I like that.
Arch your ass, go on your knees,
yes, okay, good.
And backside.
Look back. Okay. Ass out. Come on!
You take it in the ass. Show me.
Hey everybody, it's Joy Smalls.
I just wanted to let you guys know
that I'm here in LA,
and I am tested and ready
to suck some fucking dick.
Knock it off.
Hey everybody, it's Joy.
Just wanted to let you guys know
that I'm in LA,
I just got tested yesterday
and I also went on a bunch of go-sees.
I can't wait to show you guys whose
dick I'm gonna be sucking later on.
Um, if you want to recommend me
to any other companies
just put them
in the comment section below.
We're gonna do about 100 pictures each.
This is the actual studio space.
Make-up is over there.
This is Claudio, he'll do your photos.
Beautiful. Like that. Like that.
Then another hour and a half,
be outta here.
- 'Sup, Nick?
- What's up, Mike?
Oh, my God. Great.
- Who's the girl?
- That's the new Spiegler Girl.
Beautiful. Look there, straight.
Yes, like that.
Good. Good.
Brand-new.
Beautiful. My God,
you're amazing. Yes, yes, yes!
Beautiful. Great. Yes, yes, yes.
What's a Spiegler Girl?
Beautiful. Great.
Let's get you guys in make-up, okay?
- Sophia, Ava needs some touch-up.
- Oh, okay, of course.
Ava, come on over.
Bella, you guys mind switching
for a couple minutes? Perfect.
- Hello.
Oh! You're the new Spiegler
Girl. Congratulations, dude.
That's big.
So, how long have you been in LA?
Two weeks.
Oh, that must be why I haven't
seen you before. Brand-new.
How do you like it so far? Hmm?
Seeing the sights? Making some friends?
I'm not here to make friends,
I'm here to work.
All right. Perfect.
You look amazing, babe.
- Thank you.
- Come on out.
Bella, come on over.
There you go.
What a fucking bitch.
"I'm not here to make friends,
I'm here to work."
Jesus Christ,
where's a ball gag when you need one.
No, no, no. Go back in the same position.
No, the leg. This leg like this.
Closer to you, the foot. The foot!
And open the knee.
Curve on the other side.
Yes! Okay.
Okay, let me see the butt.
Okay, feet together. Bend the knees.
Okay, knees together.
Bend them at the same level.
Stick the butt out. Arch,
arch, and face to me.
Boom, like that. Yes. Kind of.
Give me the smile,
give me the smile. A nice smile!
Come on! Show sexy, be sexy.
Okay, go sideways. Like...
the face down like this.
And look at me.
Look at me, open your elbow.
Yeah. Put your... Arms back, yes.
Hey!
No-one takes pictures for free.
All right, here's how
we're gonna do this. You ready?
So... your elbow like this. Arm down.
Bup, bup, bup.
There we go. You're so beautiful.
You need a little more confidence.
And then for the butt shot.
Spin around! Pop it out.
Put that leg like... Knee. Yay!
God, look at you.
You got a little butt on ya.
All right,
now turn your head. Drop your shoulder.
- Okay. Okay. Keep going.
- You got this. You're beautiful!
Good, good, now it's good. Good.
Fucking look at her lanky ass.
She's like so skinny, I guarantee you
100% that she does fucking blow.
Probably.
Her beaver-ass looking teeth.
Fucking bitch.
So, what's a Spiegler Girl?
Oh, God.
They're like, um, they're like
the A-listers of porn, basically.
- What do you mean?
- It's like, um...
He's just pretty much one of the best
agents you could ever possibly have.
But you do work every day
and he kind of
doesn't let you have any limits
as far as what you wanna do,
- But he's...
- You have to do everything?
You have to do everything.
But it's pretty much guaranteed stardom.
- So, what's your real name?
- Um, Linnéa.
- What's yours?
- Katie.
Perfect.
You are so fucking pretty. I hate you.
But, you know.
All right,
are you ready to make a banana happy?
This is, like, an old man's banana.
Okay, I'm sorry, but not everything
is all sunshine and sparkles.
We work with what we got.
- All right.
- Suck it!
There we go.
Maybe some old man will really like this.
Oh...yes!
Fucking perfect. Can you put
it down... Can you deep throat?
Oh, my God. She's a natural!
Spit on it.
- Mm.
- Oh, my God.
You're like, "Oh, you gonna
make me swallow it?"
- You gonna make me swallow it?
- Yeah!
Now, like, pinch your nose
and roll your head back and do that.
There you go. And then swallow.
Perfect.
Oh, my God. You are so cute.
Okay, I want the part
where I put the big part in.
Here's the thing. I can actually
chop this up into different clips
and you can sell these.
♪ Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to you. ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Ashley
- ♪ Happy birthday to you. ♪
- Oh, thank you.
- I hate you guys.
- We hate you too!
It's really nice.
Sorry.
- Go, go!
- Keep sucking, keep sucking.
Yes.
Amazing job.
Have any of you guys
done squirting scenes yet?
- Well, obviously, veteran over here.
- Fuck off.
Veteran over here has probably
rained all over California.
You talk shit about being
a cougar, but I fuck young hot guys.
You just wait.
One time Mike sent me on...
...a fake shoot.
But it was like an actual private.
I went to this hotel room,
there was no crew, just one guy.
Right? Just this dude alone.
And I was like,
"All right, this is weird.”
He just had a camera with a tripod.
He made me fill out fake paperwork
and everything.
Wait, what?
We fucked, he paid me in cash,
and he never even turned the camera on.
Did you tell Mike?
He knows what he's doing.
He knows what he did.
But, I mean, it was cash, so...
So?
You know what?
A pyjama party is just a really good
excuse to run around naked. So...
Come give me my birthday lap dances.
Mmm. That's right, let me in.
You're just a soft squishy
baby that wants to be loved.
Give me my birthday spankings.
Mmm. You're my best friend.
- It's you and me, right?
- Right.
Yes...
Joy, come drink with us.
We're pre-gaming.
- We're gonna take over this shit.
- Taking over.
Does everyone have their asses out?
Mike's going to be like,
"Make a good impression."
I don't know what he means
by that. I've tried everything.
Sorry, we're drunk.
Get your ass out
of my face before I eat it.
Hey, Bella, how many dicks
are you gonna suck tonight?
Come on, bitch!
Who wants to pull their dick out? Come on,
I want more alcohol.
Time to pose! Time to pose!
Woo!
They think they can
just cut line like that?
I'm just gonna say hi to my friend.
Where are you going?
- Hey!
It's so good to see you.
Oh, my goodness. Sorry, excuse me.
- So, you excited to be here?
- Yeah, networking.
You ready for it?
This is Aiden Starr,
she's a great director for Kink.
Hi, I'm Bella.
- Very brand-new.
- Nice to meet you.
She's into the stuff you like to shoot,
I think you guys should talk.
- I would love to work with you.
- Oh, all right, cool.
Go get your picture taken. Go ahead.
- Perfect, good shot.
- Right over here.
Smile.
We should totally take a selfie.
VIP only.
Please step aside.
- Where you been?
- Where have you been, girl?
I just... I met a friend.
Or was it a...
It was a friend.
Oh, my God, you guys.
I wanna go talk to Caesar so bad!
That guy's a dick, dude.
Yeah, but he's so hot! What?
- This is your time to shine.
- My time to shine?
All right, fine.
I need more liquid courage.
I feel like I drink champagne
and you never drink at all...
Hi.
Oh. Hey.
We met at the photo
shoot a couple weeks ago.
Oh. It's good to see you again.
So, uh, no pyjamas?
No. I have a big shoot tomorrow
so I'm going to leave soon.
It's nice to see you again.
Nice to see you too.
What's wrong with you,
you little piece of shit?
There's no need to be
rude. You can talk to me.
Did we work together or something?
No,
I'm just a huge fan. I'm in the industry.
That's cool.
What the fuck?
So, just go back
to the fucking trailer park,
where trash like you belong,
and leave me alone.
Did you just call me trailer trash?
Yes. Specifically.
All right. Fuck you, prop dick!
Fuck you, motherfucker.
I'll fucking kill you, bitch.
You wanna fucking fight?
No, get your hands off me.
Get your fucking hands off me!
Let me at that little bitch! Ashley,
Kimberley, get my shit!
Bella!
Is he okay?
Yeah?
Hi, my name is Bella Cherry,
I want to talk to Mark Spiegler.
You got him.
- I want to be a Spiegler Girl.
- So does everybody.
Well, I'm not like everybody.
I came here all the way from Sweden.
- I'm here to be the next big porn star.
- Okay...
You won't find anyone like me.
I'm not like the rest of these girls.
All right. Hold on.
You're cute, but on the Adult Direct site
it says you only do solo,
girl-girl, and boy-girl.
Most of our girls are known
for being really hardcore,
that's our type of girl,
and you don't sound perverted
or anything like that to me,
which is also our type of girl...
But I'm brand-new,
I'm just getting started,
Besides that, your social media is,
like, pretty small,
you have no following, no fan base yet,
no... no anything.
! liked your nerve when you called,
but what we're looking for are girls
that really stand out from the crowd.
And to be honest,
I don't really think you do.
Are you really gonna
let this fucking break you?
I'm not fucking broken.
I'm just not interested in seeing
that sign. I know what it looks like.
- My dog hasn't seen the sign.
- I don't care about your dog.
What the fuck?
Don't you wanna see anything
else in LA besides a fucking porn set?
No.
Hello!
- Hey.
- Come here.
Oh, man, you look fucking great.
You, uh, you're much taller
than last time I saw you.
Look at that.
Oh, it matches her outfit.
It's fucking beautiful!
Turn around. Thank you so much.
- Is that too tight, babe?
- No.
Do you want it tighter?
Turn around, let me see.
Fuck yeah! Is it uncomfortable?
Mm-mm.
Um, can we call you names?
Like slut, bitch, whore, things like that?
Does that bother you? Do you
not have any feelings about it?
Or does it turn you on?
Okay, put that on
and just slide it up like that.
So basically you get to pick
what kind of shark you are
and then it plops you out
in the streets of New York
and you swim around and
you fucking cause mayhem
and you eat everything
and then it gives you powers
and it's really fucking cool.
You can customise the colours
and put little names on 'em.
- Do I smell like onions?
- No, you're...
Are you sure?
- I feel like I stink.
- No, you're fine.
Look, see.
That one's kind of cute, like you.
- It's a cute shark!
- It's a shark.
If you make eye contact with me,
I'll be behind you with
the light the whole time,
so make eye contact,
I'll also have the lube.
Watch your head.
- Lean on back.
- Thanks everybody.
Nice and centred.
I'm just gonna
hold your head here.
You can just rest your head.
I know you stretched before but
if you stretch after you get out of it
then it will really
help you not feel sore.
- Okay.
- It's not like a painful sore.
It's like "you went to the gym" sore.
Uh,
do you remember your safe words?
Yes, "red" is stop.
Red is stop completely.
If there's a gag in your mouth you go,
"Uh-uh-uh."
If you need stuff to slow down,
if he's slapping you or choking
you or hitting you with an implement,
do you remember what the word
you use is to ask him to slow down?
- "Yellow" or "mercy".
- Perfect!
Also, if you can't speak,
you can just give me a little
tap and that means "chill out."
She definitely can't tap you.
- Hmm. You can kick me.
- I'll use my feet.
Got her? Nice and slow.
- Good? Everything feeling okay?
- Yeah.
It looks so good.
Yeah. I wish I could see
what it looks like.
Get in there and really connect with her.
I wanna see a lot of chemistry.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Can we have some lube
for his masturbation purposes?
Is there lube anywhere?
Okay, step out.
Start right in with the verbal.
Action!
Look at me.
Why are you here?
Why am I here?
Why are you laughing?
Why are you fucking laughing?
Look at this. Open your mouth.
Good. Ramp up the energy.
Now, I've punished you a little bit,
just a little bit,
do you think you deserve a reward yet?
Yes, sir.
- Do you like the way that feels?
- Mm-hm.
- Do you want more of it?
- Yeah. Yes, sir.
How you doing down there, honey?
You good?
- Yeah.
- Say it louder. Are you good?
Yes, sir.
Open your eyes.
If you're gonna cum, you're gonna
fucking look at me. Yes, you are.
Get her there. Make her cum.
Here you go.
Would you like to take a shower?
Or do you want to relax and lay
down on the couch for a while?
- I want to relax.
- Here's your water. Drink the water.
We'll put this robe on you. Robe!
Great job!
There's no way to learn.
I have this overbite,
I think it's from sucking too many dicks.
What's that?
- So...
- Glass noodles.
I already called Mike and asked
him to book me for more rough scenes
because I found my niche,
I'm very submissive.
Oh! Then why do you act
like such a bitch all the time?
Fuck you.
In bed! In bed.
No, but I loved it, it was great.
- Who was the director?
- Aiden Starr.
Holy shit! Where'd you meet her?
Mm. I met her at the party.
- Argh!
- The party.
Fuck that party.
My birthday party,
where I got the best present ever,
that dickhead Caesar
getting thrown in the pool.
It was so funny.
That guy's a fucking douchebag.
I will punish the shit out of him.
People need to know that guy's a dick.
He should get blacklisted
from the industry
'cause nobody touches
my baby girls like that,
that's really fucked up.
No-one talks shit to my girls.
Right, Joy? See. I got you, girl.
I got your back.
It's, like, fuck these guys.
I wish that...
We should all just start our own company,
find a rich investor or a sugar daddy.
And, just, you know, all girls,
get really fat and ugly,
and then, if guys want to work,
they have to eat our pussies...
under our fat flap.
While we eat Chinese food!
Fat flap?
Where is your fat flap, I wonder?
She's just saying women
should have more power
in what happens to them at work.
But I'm also say...
hinting at the fat fucks
who expect us to go over there
and fuck them to get work.
Yeah. I don't wanna fuck
fat fucks any more.
- You ready?
- Sing to me.
♪ Johnny var Evas hjärtas laga.
♪ Han var solen när det dagas.
♪ Han var parken när det våras
♪ Do-do-do, do, do... ♪
I know this part.
♪ Och vi satt på gräset
♪ Som växte I takt med himlen.
♪ Bengen drog förbi sen
♪ Bengen trålar än
♪ Johnny, du och jag borde
starta upp ett band
♪ Och låta det explodera i skyn
♪ Det är svårt att inte grata
♪ När jag tänker på oss två nu... ♪
- Woo!
- Damn.
♪ För du var solskenet och... ♪
♪ Jag var ensam. ♪
Yeah!
Yay!
- Encore.
- That was good.
Why aren't you doing something better
with your life and trying to be a singer?
I just love cock.
Oh, my God!
- You find everything? Got parking?
- Yeah.
- I know it's a bit far out. Sorry.
- It's fine.
And this skirt. And this little crop top.
Know what? You just go ahead and pick.
You've got good
taste. You'll figure it out.
Don't forget to fill out
all the paperwork, IDs,
go ahead and get changed and,
like I said, the talent's already on set.
- When you're ready, just come on back.
- All right.
- You're gonna have a good time today.
- Yeah.
- Hey. All right.
- Hi.
Have a seat.
So, um, today you know it's going
to be a bit of a rough scene. Right?
- Yeah.
- You're cool with a rough scene?
- You like that kind of stuff?
- Yes.
So the choking, spanking,
uh, spitting, slapping,
all that stuff is good
for you? Hair pulling?
- Yeah, that's fine.
- Cool.
I'm going to roll. You ready?
- Mm-hmm.
- Awesome.
And... action.
Oh, you must be
real proud of yourself, huh?
Sucking dick for money?
You're gonna be a superstar, baby.
We're gonna have some fun with you.
- Get the fuck up.
- Give me the whore. Right here.
Back down.
Look. Open your fucking eyes
and look at him.
- You want that, bitch?
- Oh, yeah.
Are you laughing?
Oh, you think this is fucking funny?
You think this is funny, huh?
We'll show you how fucking funny it is.
Huh? Is it fucking funny, whore?
I'm talking to you, bitch!
What are you being so silent for?
Hey, wake the fuck up!
Come on, talk!
Look at him. See that?
You're gonna suck his fucking dick today,
know that?
You're gonna choke
and throw up all over it.
Come here.
Come on.
Tell me how much you love it.
I wanna hear it.
Beg me for it, baby. Beg me for it.
- Ooh, what do you...
- Stop!
Look at me, look at me.
- Put the fucking hands down.
- Give me those eyelids.
Stop!
Okay, okay, cut.
Oh, hey.
- Are you okay?
- You okay?
Take a little breather.
You're doing great.
Let's get you up.
You're doing amazing.
- Help her onto the couch.
- Come on.
Good job. That's nice.
- Some water or something?
- Good.
You okay?
You knew this was a rough scene, right?
Yeah. Uh...
A little intense?
Told you it'd be rough. Okay?
You okay, honey?
I mean, it's just a show.
- You're killing it.
- You're tough.
Just wanna
make sure you're comfortable.
- Yeah.
- She does like a rough scene?
Just take a breath,
we got a minute, no problem.
We do have to start all over again, right?
I can probably pick it up from here.
But if you can, try not to stop this time.
If you need to, okay.
But let's try not to stop.
- Okay. Yeah.
- Okay? You good?
- I'm gonna start on the close-up, guys.
- Let's rock this!
And... let's go.
On the goddamn floor.
On the floor. Crawl. Like we said, crawl!
Come on.
Let's see easy. Let's do it.
Doesn't she look tasty?
Yeah, let me get that.
Come here, give me that.
Bitch.
Come on.
Oh, yeah, you like that, huh?
Got your fucking hands.
Oh, yeah.
Stop!
All right, all right.
Look.
Just take a second, okay?
Everything will be all right.
Just relax.
You're okay.
Nothing's happening to you now, okay?
Let me see those pretty eyes.
You're gonna be okay.
You're a very strong girl.
It's all right.
Nothing's gonna happen.
You don't have to do it.
You don't have to do
anything you don't want to do.
You're incredible.
You're very strong.
You're very extreme.
You're doing an incredible scene.
You wanna finish, don't you?
Just take some deep breaths.
It's going to be an amazing scene, honey.
Okay? Take some deep breaths.
You started off good, right?
- Yes?
- Yeah.
So what do you think?
Think we can get you
cleaned up a little bit,
jump out there and just get it finished?
It's all we gotta do.
You think that's something you can do?
I personally believe in you,
I think you can get it done.
And I know these guys
are really professional.
Okay.
- I couldn't hear you. What was that?
- Okay.
Is that a yes?
Feels good to say yes, right?
Yeah...
Okay, let's get you cleaned up
and then we'll finish this.
It'll be over before you know it. Okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Come on.
Actually, no.
Can I go?
- What?
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- What do you mean?
- Can I leave? I don't want to do it.
Yeah, you wanna go, go.
It's fine. Look, there's the door.
Hell, we'll even help you with your bags,
don't even worry about it.
This is what you chose to do, right?
Right? You chose to be here today, yeah?
You can do whatever you want
but you need to understand something.
You're fucking
with everybody else's money.
You think I'm gonna pay
for half of a scene?
How am I gonna do that?
That means everything you just did
was for nothing. For free.
Don't know what the hell
I was thinking anyway.
It's not for everybody.
So, that's fine. You wanna go, leave.
Why didn't you call me?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
I told you specifically,
if anything changes on set.
I don't care if the male talent changes,
if they move location,
if they decide they want to change
your hairstyle, you call me immediately.
I was scared! What was I supposed to do?
I was by myself with three men!
Scared of what? Is there a...
Scared of them fucking hurting me
when they were raping me for hours!
- What the fuck do you think?
- Stop it.
You don't just throw that word
around because you had a bad shoot.
You shot a rough scene? Okay.
Something you can't handle? Okay.
But everything you consented...
So, you're like them?
You're taking their side?
- No.
- You're my agent!
- You're supposed to have my back.
- I have your back.
Obviously, you do not.
You asked me specifically
for rough scenes.
I sat down with you right fucking there.
You said you wanted hair pulling,
something rough,
you could handle this, you're from Sweden,
you're better than all the other girls.
All that other bullshit.
I listened to you.
I explained to you to look
at the website prior to going on set.
Did you look at the website?
You know what?
You can go fuck yourself.
You're upset. I get that.
No. I'm finished, I'm done.
I'm done with you.
- Yeah, you can't handle this.
- Go to hell.
Get the fuck outta my office.
I'm more than glad to.
- Hello?
- Hey, Mom.
Hi, sweetheart.
Can I move back home?
How's the internship?
Has something happened?
Nothing's happened.
I just want to leave.
You've got to tell me.
I can hear that you're upset.
It's just all a bit much.
I just can't take it any more.
Ah, sweetie.
I mean...
...of course you can come
home whenever you like, but...
it just feels like
you're rushing info things.
When we spoke the other day,
everything sounded so good.
You'd met some new friends.
Have you been fighting with someone?
No, nothing's happened.
I just can't take it any more.
Everyone here is just fucking insane.
Mm.
Do you remember you wanted to leave
Sweden because everyone was insane?
I mean...
I don't know what's happened, but...
...unfortunately,
you'll come across idiots everywhere.
You just need to learn
how to deal with them.
There'll always be people
who want to bring you down.
Or say you can't.
Especially if you're a young woman.
This is your life, Linnéa.
You're in charge.
And when you've made your mind up,
you can do anything.
I know that.
Maybe you should try to get some sleep.
Try to get some sleep now
and we'll speak tomorrow.
Then we can see how you feel.
Black.com, this is Tom,
how can I help you?
Hi, my name is Bella Cherry,
um, I want to talk to the person
in charge of the bookings.
Yeah, this is him. How can I help you?
I was wondering if you
book without agents?
Mm, not really. You need a secure
company. Do you have your own company?
No, I don't, but...
What if I would do it for free?
Yeah, I can't do Friday.
I could do Wednesday.
Tues... Yeah?
All right, Wednesday it is.
There you are. Okay,
we need to get you into make-up
because we need to cover up these tattoos.
Just go upstairs
and Mike will take care of you.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Nice. Perfect. I love the outfit.
Thanks.
This is your co-star, Jason.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. I'm Bella.
Wow, you are so much taller
with the shoes. Can you lose 'em?
Outfit looks great without them.
I got them.
Yeah. There you go.
Perfect. This is better.
- Awesome!
- Yeah.
I gotta go downstairs
and make a phone call.
You guys relax, okay.
For sure.
Hi! I'm Bella.
I'm about to get
two Black dicks up my ass.
And you find this funny?
It's not gonna be funny when you're done.
Come on.
No, but for real, like, you requested me
for this extreme scene?
Yes, of course.
I don't want to hurt you. Like...
You're not hurting me, you're helping me.
And I've prepared.
- I like your style!
- Yeah, they put me in this.
It's great. I love it. Billionaires Club.
Something's wrong with you.
I don't know what's wrong with you.
Bella's playing a Hollywood rich girl
and her parents went away
on another vacation.
This is your time to fulfil your fantasy.
You got the house all to yourself,
you called the guys you
wanted to get fucked by,
today you're gonna get
two big black cocks in your ass.
This is what you wanted,
we're gonna bring it to everybody,
and I'm excited.
- You did all your girlie things?
- I did all my girlie things.
Okay. Do you need water or anything?
- No, I'm good.
- Awesome. Where's Bear?
I haven't seen him, man.
Bear...
Whoa.
Don't you guys knock in Sweden?
- What is that?
- Uh... nothing.
Don't... It was nothing at all.
Okay, um, I use that
to keep my dick hard in a scene.
Um, I'd really appreciate it
if you didn't tell anybody.
Of course.
Know what I said earlier? Forget
about it. You're gonna Kill this scene.
Okay.
Mmm. I want two black dicks up my ass.
You guys are impressed, great ass.
There you go. It's MOS,
don't worry about it.
Feeling her up, touching her shoulders.
There you go, Bella,
feel around their waist,
this is what you've been wanting.
There you go.
Bella, you're moving your ass around,
your hips.
Good? Does anyone need water?
- Bella, you good?
- Yeah, I'm good.
You look beautiful. You're doing awesome.
- I'm gonna try it again, okay?
- Okay.
Just breathe.
- Take your time with it.
- Take a deep breath. It's okay.
- Just... a little slow.
- Okay.
Okay. I'm gonna stay still.
Do you trust me?
- I trust you.
- Okay.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Breathe.
You're doing great.
Okay. Okay.
- It's okay...
- Wait.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Focus on me while he's getting ready.
It's gonna feel like a pinch,
but, once you get past that point,
it'll be a little bit easier, okay.
There we go.
Okay, you're doing good.
Okay, breathe, breathe, breathe.
I'm gonna ease it in a little more. Okay.
Just keep it going. There you go.
There you go, there you go,
right there, right there, right there.
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
You're a rich white girl
taking two dicks. Yeah.
It's all yours, use it.
Yeah, take this Black dick.
Oh, yeah.
Taking this big Black cock like a champ.
It's okay. Mmm.
And your ass is still so fucking tight.
Bella, look at the camera.
You didn't know
what you were getting into.
Oh, God, it's so big.
This what you want?
Yeah. Fuck me harder!
- Oh, yeah, right there.
- Oh, my God.
- Hey. Come on in.
- Hi.
Have a seat.
Hold on.
Hello. Yeah, well, listen,
I don't give a fuck.
The girls talk amongst themselves
and I hear them talk about it.
So, if it happens again,
something very bad is gonna happen to you.
That's it.
Okay.
The reason I am here
is because I want a serious agent.
Okay.
I know you're serious,
I know you're the best agent,
and I won't settle for anything less.
- Mark!
- Yo.
- Hi, Mark.
- Come on in.
- How's it going?
- Okay, so far.
- Who's this?
- This is Bella.
- Hi.
- Hey, Bella!
- She wants to be a Spiegler Girl.
- Are you scaring her?
- Me?
- Yes.
No, I'm cute and cuddly.
He is, actually.
Go ahead, tell us about yourself.
I wanna be like you.
Because you are the best.
She's done double-anal already.
- Damn.
- Really?
Yeah.
My first anal.
Interracial as well.
Your first anal
scene was a double-anal?
It's never been done before.
- I'm very impressed.
- I'm still working on regular anal.
You'll get there.
One day, Mark.
So, my video on Black
already has 700,000 views.
- In what length of time?
- In a week.
That's pretty good.
And I already have 10,000
new followers on Instagram.
- Oh.
So, you're pretty much brand-new.
Yeah. Brand-new.
- She's cute.
- Yeah, she is cute.
- He's like, "So what?"
- Cute's not everything.
I know, but...
We don't want girls that
are here for just for the money.
I'm not in it for...
money or...
Obviously, yes, it's a lot of fun,
and it's adventurous,
and I like that.
But mostly I'm a performer.
I love being in front of the camera,
I love having people watching me.
I want an agent who's serious about this
and obviously, it goes both ways.
I'll stay loyal as long
as you have my back.
- You should take her.
- You should.
We approve.
We like her. I think she's the real deal.
Okay,
we'll take you on a trial basis.
I'll make a decision after the expo.
In Vegas, this is at the AVN.
I've done this with girls
where they were unofficial,
but I've gotten them a few jobs
to see how they do. Cool?
It's very difficult
to become a Spiegler Girl.
Can I get a sponge?
I'm very strict about business.
You know, there's three jobs here.
There's sucking and fucking.
And the two important ones:
Don't make us look bad,
and don't give us shit to worry about.
There we are.
See if you can slide back over here.
There we go, face me.
Chin up just a little bit.
There we go. Perfect.
Head down just a tad.
What are you doing, man?
Come on. Whose bad idea was this?
- What if she falls in the pool?
- She's fine.
I can't risk her getting her hair wet.
Okay, good.
- All right.
- I'm just gonna need a second. Okay?
Sorry, guys. Just a sec.
Hey, um, would it be weird
if I asked to, like, lick your feet?
Would that bother you?
- No, that's fine.
- It's okay? All right.
Thank you. I know it's weird, but...
Um...
Fuck.
So when we call you,
you always gotta answer the phone.
And also, when you show up on a set,
you represent us.
So, you know, you're not whiny,
you're not bitchy, and no drama.
What do you mean "cheers"? It's "skål".
Skål!
I'm happy for you,
but I don't want you to leave me.
You guys should leave Mike too.
Yeah...right.
You're gonna give me advice now?
You should take control over your shit.
You're just going from one pimp
to another pimp, you know that, right?
You've already done double-anal,
so everybody's gonna
want to be booking you
for crazier and crazier shit.
Well, I can make a career
with a pink sock.
It's a thing!
But isn't Mike gonna go there?
No, I don't think he can afford a booth.
- Oh, well.
You can stay with me.
That would be really nice.
I might take you up on that.
- You should.
- Just to kind of mingle.
Yeah, stay in my room. A fancy hotel room.
- For free.
- If it's for free...
- It's for me.
God.
Some quality time in Vegas, baby.
'Cause I guess, at this point,
I'm just a blown-out whore, you know.
Five children that are just
gonna shoot out like a cannonball.
You know, after three months,
all the cocks in the industry
have just ran through it.
"Ran through it."
- Like a fucking bulldozer.
- Yeah.
You know, I can recommend you
for some scenes.
Oh, boy.
You don't want to do scenes with me?
Bitch. This is hot. I will burn you.
I will.
Maybe you can shove it up my pussy
and close it back together.
- Maybe people will want to fuck me again.
- Re-virginized!
- Stop.
- No, you stop.
Just stop being mean.
Get on your
fucking side of the bed.
I am on my goddamned side.
Shh!
Mmm. It's you and me.
- Taking over.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
- I'll cuddle myself.
- You don't have to push your butt at me.
That's how I sleep. Stop.
Can you just be on your side of the bed?
- Can you please just love me?
- No.
- Please?
- Just... Yes, thank you.
- There you go. You fucking happy now?
- Yes.
Holy shit, this place is nice.
Come out.
Holy shit,
dude. I can't believe you did this for me.
Why wouldn't I?
I'm not used to people being
nice to me. You have to understand.
All right, now be sexy.
- I love you.
- Ugh.
There you are. Hey,
there. Good to see you again.
- Good to see you too.
- How are you?
- Hi, I'm Axel.
- I'm Joy.
- Nice to meet you Joy.
- You too.
I've got some bad news and some good news.
Bad news is we lost the guy,
had to replace him last minute.
Good news is I managed to get you
the best guy in the business.
Caesar Rex,
I'm sure you've heard the name.
He's the best.
There he is!
- It's been good.
- Thanks for coming last minute.
I am so fucked.
Just act professional. Take it easy.
- Girls, Caesar Rex.
- Hey.
This is Bella, you might know Joy already.
- Hi!
- Yeah, good... good to see ya.
I'm just gonna go set it up.
When you're ready, give it 5-10 minutes,
upstairs in the big room.
What are you doing here?
It's a boy-girl-girl.
Uh, Bella requested me.
I'm really looking forward to our scene.
It doesn't matter
what you do for a living,
you have bad days at work.
Just see this as a bad day.
You'll get through it. Okay?
- Okay.
- It'll be great for your career.
Yeah.
- The location we shoot Thursday.
- I think it'll work there a lot better.
We just can't... we have major OT issues.
How do you like this?
It's great. Thank you, sweetheart,
that looks really good.
- Where's the other girl?
- Uh, I don't know. I can go get her.
- Please. Thank you.
- Yeah.
So, as long as we don't go past six...
Don't act like
you don't fucking want it.
You were practically
begging for it the other night.
Get off me!
Hey, don't fucking push me away!
Hey. Bella!
- Hi.
- See you soon.
What's going on?
I don't think I can go through with it.
Joy, you're so tough and you're so strong.
You're gonna get through this day, okay.
It's you and me.
We do this together.
Action!
Look at me.
Lick my fucking shoe.
You're so beautiful.
Lick the other shoe.
Trailer trash.
Look at me.
I know you want the cock,
but now you're just getting the shoe.
Understand?
- Yes.
- Good.
Lick.
That's what you get.
You get the fucking shoe right now.
That's what you're worth.
Fuck you.
- Ow!
- That too much?
You okay?
I really believe
that he's intentionally trying to hurt me.
He's purposefully grabbing me
and digging his claws into me.
Come on, Axel. That's ridiculous.
He's been harassing me
this whole time.
In the kitchen.
Oh, in the kitchen!
Bella, fucking please tell Axel
what he did to me. You saw everything.
Axel, how long
have we been working together?
I've never bad-touched
a woman on your set.
Okay, what is she talking about?
Bella, what did you see in the kitchen?
Tell Axel. Tell him
what happened in the kitchen.
Come on, you know me.
I don't do bad touches.
- Please...
- This bitch is crazy.
It was...
It was only a bad joke, okay?
What?
No. No.
Dude...
- No. Fuck you!
- Whoa.
I fucking hate you! Fuck you!
You stupid bitch!
I hope this industry gives you
everything you ever asked for,
you fucking whore!
Guys, I don't need this fucking drama
on my set. What the fuck?
It always happens
with this fucking idiot agent.
I can't do business with him any more.
I guess let's turn it
into a boy-girl scene.
Are you okay turning it
into a boy-girl scene?
You did great.
- Bye, guys, thank you so much.
- Great work.
What the fuck...
Hey, guys, this is Bella Cherry,
I'm in Vegas right now
and I'm getting eat... ready...
Hey, guys, this is Bella Cherry,
I'm in Vegas right now
and I'm getting ready for AVN tomorrow.
- Hi.
- Can I get a picture?
Yeah, for sure.
- Autograph?
- Yeah.
Hey, is that Ava?
Hey, can I get a picture of you?
Oh, that's beautiful. Fantastic.
Yeah, right over here!
Perfect, you guys are dressed.
Look at you. Good to see you,
Ava, again. Beautiful.
- Very nice. And hi, Bella.
- Hi.
- You look beautiful too.
- Thank you.
All right, so you guys are ready?
We're gonna start with some stills.
Okay, sit down.
Maybe... You know what?
Move a little bit more on the bed.
Face each other at first. Good.
- How do we look with the lighting?
- Looks great.
Let me see.
You guys stay like this. It's perfect.
All right, girls. Let's continue.
Ava, you're gonna take
Bella's panties off. Is that okay?
Do it nice and sexy.
You're gonna capture this
in the pictures? So, do it now.
That's so beautiful. I really like that.
And now, Ava, go in between her legs
and eat her out like there's no tomorrow.
Okay, um, I'm sorry, but it's just...
Her pussy is just...
It's... She has a really intense
cream situation going on down there.
Okay, no problem.
Can you please bring a douche
and give it to Bella?
Bella, just take the douche
and go in the rest room.
Actually, um, it kind of smells too.
I think she has a yeast infection.
Okay, um, no problem.
We're gonna fix this very easy.
Here. Put this on.
We're just gonna change the scene
into a strap-on scene,
Ava, you don't have to go down to her,
and, Bella, you're just gonna fuck Ava.
Is that okay?
You need any help, Bella?
Okay, Ava, please help Bella
to put the strap-on on.
Put the camera on the rig. Yeah.
It's over there.
All right, girls. So what I really want
you to do now is feel the passion.
Get into each other.
And, Bella,
you're going to fuck her really good.
And action.
Yeah, choke on it.
Is that how far you can go?
Look at me.
Come on.
Face down.
You're such a filthy little whore.
You like that, huh? Hmm?
Open your mouth.
Mmm. Does that taste good?
Stop!
I'm sorry.
What for?
Come on!
Can we stop the car?
Stop the car. I need to get out.